Hello, my name is Goody,
你好，我叫 古迪，
and in 1841, I was bitten by a stem vampire.
1841年，我被一个吸血鬼长辈咬了。
A stem is able to awaken the victims
他不会吸干受害者的血
they choose not to drain.
从而唤醒他们。
Normally, this would be one of those tales
通常来说，这会是一个
of gore and homicidal urges,
充满血腥和杀戮的故事，
but I've always looked on the bright side.
但我总是试图从积极的角度看待。
So I learned to live on animal blood.
所以我学会了靠动物的血液生存，
And having eternal life
并获得了永生，
gave me extra years with my loved ones.
这样我就能与所爱之人多相处一些时光。
Nighttime used to be dull and dark,
夜晚曾经是沉闷而黑暗的，
but things got a lot better in the '80s.
但到了 80 年代，一切都变得好多了。
Oh, the 1880s, that is.
哦，那是 19 世纪 80 年代。
The Industrial Revolution gave us electricity
工业革命带来了电力
and light bulbs.
和灯泡。
And suddenly, nights were as bright as daytime.
突然间，夜晚变得如同白天一样明亮。
Telephones replaced letters,
电话取代了信件，
and the new subways let you travel the whole city
新式地铁让你能穿梭整座城市
and still be in your coffin by sunrise.
仍能在日出前回到棺材。
In the 1920s, things really turned modern.
19世纪20年代，一切都变得现代。
Skirts got shorter,
裙摆变短，
jazz babies and flappers owned the night.
爵士宝贝和摩登女郎主宰夜晚。
The world belonged to the young,
世界属于年轻人，
and I was an expert at being young.
而我正是永葆青春的专家。
And then came my favorite invention--
接着是我最爱的发明——
flickers.
默片。
Chaplin, Keaton, Cagney--
卓别林、基顿、卡格尼——
and in movies, they never got any older.
在电影里他们永远不老。
I could relate.
我深有同感。
In the 1960s, I messed up.
19世纪60年代，我搞砸了。
I let my guard down
放松了警惕
After that, things started to go downhill.
之后，事情开始急转直下。
In the '70s, I kinda lost interest in dating.
70年代，我对约会失去了兴趣。
But in the '90s, my stem turned Stacy.
但90年代，我转化了斯黛西。
She was kind of lost and I took care of her.
她当时迷失自我，而我照顾她。
I taught her to get hometown soil for her coffin,
我教她为棺材准备故乡泥土，
how to use hypnotic powers,
如何使用催眠能力，
and how to find the jugular on a rodent.
如何在啮齿动物身上找到颈静脉。
And she taught me about e-mail,
而她教我使用电邮、
Napster, and this great group,
Napster和这个超棒的乐队——
Green Day.
绿日。
So we have lots of fun.
我们玩得很开心。
We party with normal kids, we go to college.
和普通孩子聚会，一起上大学。
I've got over 10,000 credits.
我修了上万学分，
I could graduate if it wasn't during the day.
要不是白天上课，早该毕业了。
I love having a friend,
我珍视这份友谊，
or "bestie," as she calls it.
或她所谓的"闺蜜情"。
And, aw, look how cute she is.
看，她多可爱。
Hey, Goody.
嘿，古迪。
Goody, wake up. It's sunset.
古迪，醒醒。日落了。
The only bad thing about Stacy
斯黛西唯一的缺点
are her practical jokes,
就是爱搞恶作剧，
which she thinks are way funnier than they actually are.
她总觉得自己比实际更有趣。
What?
什么？
No, you didn't.
不，你没有。
Come on, let me out.
快放我出去。
- You got me
- Again.
- 又被你耍了
- 再次。
Hurry, I've got an 8:00 class.
快点，我八点有课。
Hey, Stacy. Your friend from Boston
斯黛西，你波士顿的朋友
sent your hometown soil.
寄来了故乡的泥土。
Oh, thank God.
谢天谢地。
I hardly have any left. My back has been killing me.
我几乎快没钱了。我的背疼得要命。
"We're sorry but your package has
“很抱歉，您的包裹在
accidentally been harmed in delivery."
运送过程中意外受损。”
I think the Post Office x-rays everything now,
我想邮局现在会对所有东西进行X光检查，
and this looked suspicious so they opened it.
这个看起来可疑，所以他们就打开了。
But this is just dirt.
但这只是泥土。
Yeah, but you know Homeland Security.
是啊，但你知道国土安全部的。
Man, the terrorists ruined things for everybody.
天啊，恐怖分子毁了所有人的生活。
"Visit us at www--"
“访问我们的网站www--”
why do they call it visiting?
为什么他们叫它访问？
Isn't it more like "type us a letter on the computer"?
难道不更像是“在电脑上给我们打字”吗？
Visiting is when you go somewhere.
访问是你去某个地方。
Yeah, you're at one place on the Internet,
是的，你在互联网上的一个地方，
and then you go someplace else.
然后你去另一个地方。
That doesn't make any sense. Yes, it does.
那说不通。不，说得通。
So if you're reading a book and you turn the page,
那么如果你在看书，然后翻页，
are you visiting another page?
你是在访问另一页吗？
Hold on. You still can't find your mouth
等等。你还是没镜子就找不到自己的嘴吗？
without a mirror? Thank you.
没有镜子？
谢谢。
Sunrise is at 6:40.
日出时间是6:40。
You know, I put that app in your phone.
你知道，我把那个App装到你手机里了。
You don't need the almanac.
你不需要年鉴。
I like my almanac.
我喜欢我的年鉴。
What's with the mom jeans?
穿妈妈牛仔裤是怎么回事？
Jeans are jeans. Are you kidding?
牛仔裤就是牛仔裤。你在开玩笑吗？
Jeans mark your age more than a birth certificate.
牛仔裤比出生证更能暴露年龄。
Trade shoes. At least my gladiators
换鞋。至少我的角斗士凉鞋
will get you in the right millennium.
能让你进入正确的千禧年。
Those are cute. Race you.
那些很可爱。跟你赛跑。
Oh!
哦！
Took you long enough. Well, that didn't count.
你花了够长时间的。嗯，那不算。
These aren't my shoes. Excuses, excuses.
这不是我的鞋。借口，借口。
Oh, for goodness' sake.
哦，天哪。
What time does your class end? 9:30.
你的课几点结束？9:30。
Okay, then I'll meet you at work.
好的，那我上班地方见。
Oh, God. Where are you going?
哦，天哪。你要去哪里？
Come back here.
回这儿来。
Goody!
好棒！
Cradle of Filth, Ozzy Osbourne, The Cure--
污秽摇篮，奥兹·奥斯本，治疗乐队——
Ooh, where?
哦，在哪？
Oh, no. It's one of those daytime festival things.
哦，不。是那种白天的音乐节。
Whose idiot idea was it
是哪个白痴的主意
to have rock concerts during the day?
要在白天开摇滚音乐会？
Mmm. Let's check the traps.
嗯。我们去检查下陷阱。
Ugh, rats will eat anything.
呃，老鼠什么都吃。
Oh, dead one.
哦，死了一只。
Oh, trap got him?
哦，陷阱抓到的？
I think the artificial sweeteners gave him cancer.
我想是人造甜味剂让它得了癌症。
53rd Street.
第53街。
And 6th Avenue.
还有第六大道。
53rd Street and 6th Avenue.
第53街和第六大道。
Penthouse suite.
顶层套房。
We're being summoned.
我们被召唤了。
Ask me questions. Who's the stupidest person on TV?
问我问题。电视上最蠢的人是谁？
Uh, Snooki! Oh, yes. You're right.
呃，斯努基！哦，是的。你说对了。
53rd Street.
第53街。
Who's the smartest?
谁是最聪明的？
Um, House or Frylock? Who?
嗯，豪斯还是弗莱洛克？谁？
The limping doctor or the flying French fry.
那个跛脚医生还是那个会飞的炸薯条。
53rd Street.
第53街。
Okay, 53rd Street.
好的，第53街。
Don't you love Times Square?
你不爱时代广场吗？
It feels like the center of the world.
感觉像是世界的中心。
I feel like a bunch of TVs threw up.
我感觉像是一堆电视吐了。
Take a cab. What are you, walking?
打辆出租车。你干嘛呢，走路？
Okay, okay. We're coming.
好的，好的。我们来了。
What kind of mood is she in?
她心情怎么样？
I've seen worse. Has she finished feeding?
我见过更糟的。她进食完了吗？
Because we don't want to be around any of that.
因为我们不想靠近那种事。
Where are my offshoots?
我的分支们在哪儿？
There they are.
他们在那儿呢。
Look at the new fall line.
看看新的秋季系列。
Gaultier, Prada.
高缇耶，普拉达。
Dress.
裙子。
And I can never see how I look in them.
而我永远看不到自己穿上它们的样子。
What is the point of looking like this
看起来这样有什么意义
if I can never enjoy it?
如果我永远无法享受它？
Hmm?
嗯？
Oh, sucks hard. Not so nice.
哦，太糟了。不太好。
So put them on and then I will just imagine
所以把它们穿上，然后我就想象
how much better they will look on me.
它们穿在我身上会好多少。
Ivan, call Mr. Pizza Guy.
伊万，打电话给披萨先生。
I thought we were going out.
我以为我们要出去。
I feel like a pizza guy.
我想找个披萨小哥。
Oh, come on. Those clothes are wearing you.
哦，拜托。这些衣服在穿你。
Give it some juice.
给点活力。
I don't know about this one. Why not?
我不太确定这件。为什么不？
It's just not for young people.
它就是不适合年轻人。
Excuse me?
什么？
Are you telling me about being young?
你在跟我谈论年轻？
Do you have any idea
你知道
how long I have been young?
我年轻了多久吗？
She just means that, with the recession and all,
她的意思只是，随着经济衰退什么的，
girls of a certain age couldn't afford something like this.
某个年龄段的女孩买不起这样的东西。
Plus, it's fur. It's like wearing a dead animal.
再说，这是皮草。就像穿着死动物。
Okay, here's the flaw in that argument.
好吧，这个论点有个缺陷。
Why should the life of a mink
为什么一只水貂的生命
be more valuable than the life of a pigeon?
就比一只鸽子的生命更有价值？
You two drink pigeons every day.
你们俩每天都喝鸽子血。
We set them free.
我们把它们放生了。
Stacy got attached. To pigeons?
斯泰茜对它们产生了感情。对鸽子？
You know what? We never should've named them.
你知道吗？我们根本不该给它们起名字。
I know, you're so right.
我知道，你说得太对了。
I mean, how can you hurt something named Snuggles?
我的意思是，你怎么能伤害叫“依偎”的东西？
Or Mr. Doodles? Do you remember--
或者“涂鸦先生”？你还记得——
You're pathetic.
你真可悲。
Pizza guy.
披萨小哥。
Who ordered the double cheese and sausage?
谁点的双份奶酪和香肠？
You're late.
你迟到了。
They said 20 minutes or less.
他们说20分钟或更短。
You kept me waiting, you bad boy.
你让我等，你这个坏小子。
Sorry.
抱歉。
You know what happens to bad boys.
你知道坏小子会怎么样。
I hate when she's in town.
我讨厌她在城里的时候。
It's disgusting. I know.
太恶心了。我知道。
But let's just have a good time.
但我们还是好好玩吧。
- Come on, we deserve it.
- Taxi!
- 来吧，我们该享受一下。
- 出租车！
Besides, it's goth night.
再说，今天是哥特之夜。
And all the day players always dress up so cute.
而且所有的凡人都打扮得那么可爱。
We're the oldest ones here.
我们是这里最老的。
Except for this schmohawk.
除了这个傻帽莫西干。
Can I buy you ladies a drink? We never drink...
我能请你们女士喝一杯吗？我们从不喝…
mojitos.
莫吉托。
Maybe you should court someone your own age.
也许你应该去追求和你同龄的人。
Oh, did you see that cute one? Mm-hmm.
哦，你看到那个可爱的了吗？嗯哼。
Hey. Hey, Renfield.
嘿。嘿，伦菲尔德。
Adam Ant called. He wants his makeup back.
亚当·安特打来电话了。他想要回他的妆。
Oh, come on. Awaken me. I wanna live forever.
哦，拜托。唤醒我。我想永生。
Then you should try eating more broccoli.
那你应该试试多吃点西兰花。
No, I don't want to eat more broccoli. I want to be undead.
不，我不想多吃西兰花。我想成为不死族。
You are undead. You're alive.
你就是不死族。你还活着。
Yeah, stop imagining crazy ideas.
是的，别再想象那些疯狂的想法了。
No.
不。
What? Stuck-up McVainypants is here.
什么？自命不凡的家伙来了。
So what? Just ignore him.
那又怎样？不理他就行了。
Show him how much fun you're having.
让他看看你有多开心。
What? No! No pictures.
什么？不！不拍照。
Wh-- then take me.
那——那就带我去吧。
Come on. Let's just go dance.
来吧。我们去跳舞吧。
Isn't this place a little Mickey Mouse for you?
这地方对你来说是不是有点太幼稚了？
There is Donor Club in Chinatown.
唐人街有捐赠者俱乐部。
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么。
I think I can sense a real vampire.
我想我能感觉到一个真正的吸血鬼。
Vampire? That word is so cornball.
吸血鬼？这个词太老土了。
And anyone who says "cornball"
而且任何说“老土”的人
is at least 80 years old.
至少80岁了。
Okay. I just don't appreciate
好吧。我只是不喜欢
being called the V-word.
被称为那个V开头的词。
You prefer ELF?
你更喜欢ELF？
Extended Life Form, yes.
长生种，是的。
So gay.
太基了。
Hey. Hi, Ivan.
嘿。嗨，伊万。
I see you met Vadim. You know he's my stem.
我看到你遇到瓦迪姆了。你知道他是我的源头。
Oh, you're the Soviet stem.
哦，你是苏联源头。
Ukrainian.
乌克兰人。
Let's go to that club. Blood Bank.
我们去那个俱乐部吧。血库。
We don't feed off of people.
我们不吸食人血。
Oh, great.
哦，太好了。
As long as Cisserus takes care of herself.
只要西瑟勒斯照顾好自己。
Why? Anything happens to her,
为什么？她要是有什么三长两短，
your years will accrue.
你的年龄就会累积起来。
You wouldn't want
你不会想
to look your age.
看起来像你实际的年龄。
Excuse me.
失陪一下。
I am Vadim. This is Ivan.
我是瓦迪姆。这是伊万。
I'll get my coat.
我去拿我的外套。
Oh, Juicy. She is asking for it.
哦，Juicy。她这是在找事。
Yeah, I'd say so.
是的，我同意。
Listen to me.
听我说。
Vadim and Ivan are bad guys.
瓦迪姆和伊万是坏人。
I like bad guys.
我喜欢坏人。
No, you like nice guys.
不，你喜欢好人。
Don't look at them and don't talk to them.
别看他们，也别跟他们说话。
Don't talk to them.
别跟他们说话。
And remember, nice guys.
记住，好人。
Nice guys.
好人。
Guys that listen when you say stuff.
那些你说什么都听的家伙。
Guys that compliment you.
那些会称赞你的家伙。
Hey, Juicy. Where are you going?
嘿，Juicy。你去哪儿？
- Hey. We're gonna go.
- BRB.
- 嘿。我们要走了。
- 马上回来。
Um, that only works if you're leaving.
嗯，那只有在你离开的时候才管用。
"Be right back."
“马上回来。”
Oh. SL. What?
哦。SL。什么？
"So long"? Close enough.
“再见”？差不多吧。
So I tell my parents I'm coming to the city for my music.
所以我告诉我父母我要来城市搞音乐。
And they say okay, as long as I go to NYU.
他们说好吧，只要我去纽约大学。
You want?
你要吗？
No thanks. I'm already in the mood.
不了谢谢。我已经有感觉了。
So now they're all, "What about law school?"
所以现在他们都说，“法学院怎么样？”
And I go, "I told you I was coming here for my music."
我说，“我告诉过你们我是来这里搞音乐的。”
So they're, "Then why did we spend $100,000, Derek?"
所以他们说，“那我们为什么要花10万美元，德里克？”
I'm like, "You got me. You could've just gotten me
我就说，“你说得对。你们本来可以只给我买个
Pro Tools and I'd be happy. Law school is your dream,
Pro Tools我就会很高兴。法学院是你们的梦想，
not mine."
不是我的。”
And they think it's all about record deals,
他们认为这都是关于唱片合约，
but it's so different now. They're so old-fashioned.
但现在太不一样了。他们太老派了。
They just don't get it, you know?
他们就是不明白，你知道吗？
Hey, my parents believed in witches.
嘿，我父母相信女巫。
Hold on, I gotta play you something.
等等，我得给你放点东西。
Mm.
嗯。
You've got-- you've got something.
你——你脸上有点东西。
Hmm? You want a rail?
嗯？想来点？
A little bit won't hurt.
一点点不会有事的。
I gotta get out of here.
我得离开这儿了。
Hey, people can see you.
嘿，人们能看见你。
What? Nobody cares.
什么？没人关心。
Besides, the streets are wet and my shoes are suede.
再说，街上湿漉漉的，我的鞋是麂皮的。
Stacy, I kinda did something bad.
斯泰茜，我好像做了件坏事。
What? Well, this drummer guy
什么？嗯，有个鼓手
was all coked up and his nose started bleeding.
吸了可卡因，鼻子开始流血。
- Oh, no.
- I just licked a drop.
- 哦，不。
- 我只舔了一滴。
And what now? Are you jonesing? Do you have the hunger?
现在怎么样？你毒瘾犯了吗？你渴望吗？
No.
不。
I just had what came out. It wasn't even flowing.
我只是喝了流出来的。甚至没在流。
But I know it would be so much more satisfying than this whole
但我知道这会比这整个
get-dressed-go-out- and-have-sex routine.
打扮-出门-做爱流程更令人满足。
I mean, guys used to want to sing
我是说，以前的男人想唱歌
or paint or write.
或者画画或者写作。
Now, it's like iPod hits and webisodes.
现在，就像是iPod热门歌曲和网络剧集。
Half the time, I don't even know what they're talking about.
一半时间，我甚至不知道他们在说什么。
Well, we're going to group tomorrow. That always helps.
嗯，我们明天要去小组。那总是有帮助的。
Hey.
嘿。
Didn't that used to be a yogurt place?
那以前不是个酸奶店吗？
Things keep changing around here.
这儿的东西一直在变。
Well, in the '70s, it was a methadone clinic
嗯，70年代，那是个美沙酮诊所
and all the hippies would be sitting on the stairs
所有的嬉皮士都会坐在楼梯上
waiting for their medicine.
等着他们的药。
And in the '50s, it was a dance studio,
50年代，那是个舞蹈工作室，
and everyone came to the Village to be beatniks.
每个人都来到村子里当垮掉派。
And before that, it was a German newspaper.
在那之前，那是个德语报社。
How do you know this stuff?
你怎么知道这些东西？
The History Channel. Oh.
历史频道。哦。
Uh-oh, birds.
哦-哦，鸟来了。
Hurry. Go, go! Whoops!
快点。走，走！哎呀！
Get back. Watch out, Kenny!
退后。小心，肯尼！
Oh!
哦！
That's Van Helsing. Let him through.
那是范海辛。让他过去。
Oh, no, no, no. This doesn't have
哦，不，不，不。这跟
anything to do with Homeland Security
国土安全部没有任何关系
so get away from my crime scene, huh?
所以离我的犯罪现场远点，嗯？
Did you recover the neck?
你找到脖子了吗？
Look, it's your garden variety John Doe.
看，这是你那种普通的无名氏。
Killed, bled out someplace else,
被杀，在别的地方放干血，
they hacked it up and dumped it here.
他们把它砍碎然后扔在这里。
You call this bled out? It's bone dry.
你管这叫放干血？它干得像骨头一样。
Detective.
警探。
Excuse me, ma'am. I need you to back up, please.
对不起，女士。我需要你退后，拜托。
What is that, a pizza carrier?
那是什么，一个披萨外卖包？
There. You happy now?
喏。现在你满意了吗？
Hey, if we find a subway map and explosives, we'll call you.
嘿，如果我们找到地铁地图和炸药，我们会给你打电话。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Good evening. My name is Harry,
晚上好。我叫哈里，
and welcome to Sanguines Anonymous.
欢迎来到嗜血者互诫协会。
Tepish, you're a stem, aren't you?
泰皮什，你是个源头，对吧？
Someone told me that if a stem dies,
有人告诉我如果一个源头死了，
all the offshoots die.
所有的分支都会死。
It's an old wives' tale, right?
这是老太太们的传说，对吧？
I thought as long as you stayed out of the sun, you're okay.
我以为只要你不晒太阳，你就没事。
And if your stem died, you start aging.
如果你的源头死了，你会开始变老。
No, you start aging, but not like the day players.
不，你会开始变老，但不像那些凡人。
You become your chronological age.
你会变成你实际的年龄。
When were you awakened?
你是什么时候被唤醒的？
1841.
1841年。
Ah, pfft. Baby.
啊，噗。小娃娃。
Besides, 200 is the new 80.
再说，200岁是新的80岁。
Stacy turned in 1992.
斯泰茜是1992年转化的。
Does she know how old you are?
她知道你多大了吗？
No.
不。
It seemed to comfort her thinking we were the same age.
让她觉得我们同龄似乎能安慰她。
Ah, I see.
啊，我明白了。
You're from Cisserus, huh? You know her?
你是西瑟勒斯那条线上的，嗯？你认识她？
We had a fling.
我们有过一段风流韵事。
Mm.
嗯。
That took about a century off my life.
那让我少活了大概一个世纪。
Hey.
嘿。
Tepish, would you like to start off tonight?
泰皮什，你愿意今晚开始吗？
Okay.
好的。
Thank you, Harry.
谢谢你，哈里。
Hi, everyone.
大家好。
I am Vlad Tepish.
我是弗拉德·泰皮什。
You know, Vlad the Impaler.
你知道，穿刺公弗拉德。
Hi, Vlad Tepish.
嗨，弗拉德·泰皮什。
I have abstained from the fluids of homo sapiens
我已经戒除了智人的体液
for 362 years.
362年了。
I'm sure that you've heard about what I did
我相信你们都听说过我对
to the Turkish army, huh?
土耳其军队做了什么，嗯？
He impaled them.
他把他们穿刺了。
You youngsters have to learn how to substitute
你们年轻人必须学会如何用
what you can't do with things that are less harmful.
危害较小的事情来替代你们不能做的事情。
Personally, I like knitting.
就我个人而言，我喜欢编织。
Especially...
尤其是…
this part.
这一步。
Thank you, thank you. Thank you.
谢谢，谢谢。谢谢。
Hi, I'm Stacy. Hi, Stacy.
嗨，我是斯泰茜。嗨，斯泰茜。
I've been in my 20s for two decades,
我已经二十多岁二十年了，
and when I was a day player, I was doing a lot of E.
当我还是个凡人的时候，我嗑了很多E。
E? I don't know what that is.
E？我不知道那是什么。
That's ecstasy.
那是摇头丸。
And then one night, I must've been pretty stoned,
然后有一天晚上，我肯定嗨大了，
'cause I don't even remember,
因为我甚至不记得了，
but I know Cisserus was feeding on me,
但我知道西瑟勒斯在吸我的血，
and Goody was arguing that I would be a good
古蒂在争辩说我会是她很好的
clothing model for her.
服装模特。
So if it wasn't for Goody, I would be dead.
所以如果不是古蒂，我就死了。
Like, dead-dead.
就是，死透了的那种死。
But she says that I saved her because she'd been so lonely,
但她说我救了她，因为她一直很孤独，
and having a friend made her want to keep existing.
有个朋友让她想继续存在下去。
Even though I've never had human blood,
尽管我从未喝过人血，
I still feel tempted.
我仍然感到诱惑。
But it's like drugs.
但这就像毒品。
We don't need the high-highs.
我们不需要那种极度的快感。
It's more satisfying to not hurt anybody
不伤害任何人，
and just have fun with your friends.
和你的朋友们玩得开心，这样更令人满足。
- Thanks.
- Good meeting, people.
- 谢谢。
- 会议开得很好，各位。
Shall we?
我们走吧？
When it comes to drinking human blood,
当涉及到饮用人血时，
a single drop is too much,
一滴都太多，
and a whole family is never enough.
而一整个家庭也永远不够。
Support your fellow ELFs.
支持你的同伴ELF。
Undead is not unfeeling.
不死并非无情。
Great.
太好了。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Don't you hate it when you sprout fangs,
你难道不讨厌长出獠牙时，
part's white and then the other part's dingy?
一部分是白的，另一部分却脏兮兮的吗？
I never thought about it.
我从没想过。
It's Renfield.
是伦菲尔德。
Hey, Renfield! Where are you guys?
嘿，伦菲尔德！你们在哪儿？
Let's go to SoHo House.
我们去SoHo House吧。
I'm sick of these clip joints.
我受够了这些宰客的店。
How about this? You go, and if it's great, text us.
这样如何？你去，如果很棒，发短信给我们。
All right. G2G.
好吧。G2G。
G2G.
G2G。
"Got to go."
“得走了。”
Why can't kids say entire words?
为什么孩子们不能说完整的词？
It takes just as long to say letters.
说字母花的时间一样长。
Remember, we said that we'd keep up with the times
记住，我们说过要跟上时代
even though it's not as good as the '80s.
即使不如80年代好。
You don't hear me complaining every time
你没听我每次新歌出来时抱怨
a new song comes on that Devo is much better.
Devo乐队好得多。
That's true.
那是真的。
You have a glob.
你沾上了一块。
Here? Other side.
这里？另一边。
Here? A little higher.
这里？再高一点。
Doesn't it drive you crazy
难道你不抓狂吗
not knowing what you look like?
不知道自己长什么样？
You look the same as you always did.
你看起来和以前一样。
You have pictures from before. No.
你有以前的照片。没有。
You don't have any pictures from your early years?
你早年没有任何照片吗？
No.
没有。
A guy in the park drew this.
公园里有个人画了这个。
Do I look anything like this?
我看起来像这个吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
He really captured you. Oh.
他真的抓住了你的神韵。哦。
Hold on.
等等。
Okay, she sort of has your structure.
好的，她有点像你的轮廓。
You have rounder eyes,
你的眼睛更圆，
shorter chin,
下巴更短，
change the hair,
换个发型，
green eyes,
绿眼睛，
and...
还有…
fix the nose.
修一下鼻子。
And print.
然后打印。
Oh, my God.
哦，我的天。
That's me. Yeah.
那是我。是的。
It's been so long.
好久不见了。
I take back everything bad I ever said about computers.
我收回所有我说过的关于电脑的坏话。
Thank you. You're welcome.
谢谢你。不客气。
Ooh.
哦。
Good morning. Morning.
早上好。早上好。
Ew.
恶心。
Well, LASIK has come a long way.
嗯，LASIK手术已经取得了长足的进步。
Hi, I'm Joey. Hi, I'm Stacy.
嗨，我是乔伊。嗨，我是斯泰茜。
Hey, would you like to have lunch with me sometime?
嘿，你愿意什么时候和我一起吃午饭吗？
No. Okay.
不。好吧。
Um, no, what I meant was I work during the day
嗯，不，我的意思是白天我工作
but I could have coffee or drinks.
但我可以喝咖啡或饮料。
Okay, great.
好的，太好了。
All right, any questions?
好了，有什么问题吗？
Yes, Professor Quincy.
是的，昆西教授。
How many surrealists does it take to change a light bulb?
需要多少个超现实主义者才能换一个灯泡？
How many? A bicycle.
多少个？一辆自行车。
Well, thank you for that wonderful insight, Mr. Van Helsing.
嗯，谢谢你那精彩的见解，范海辛先生。
All right, I know that was no "Talladega Nights."
好了，我知道那不是《塔拉迪加之夜》。
Now what was Dalí trying to do in this?
现在达利在这里想做什么？
Stacy, don't take a nap.
斯泰茜，别打盹。
You'll be up all day.
你会醒一整天的。
I'm so tired. I was IM'ing all day.
我好累。我一整天都在发即时消息。
I barely slept.
我几乎没睡。
I met someone at school.
我在学校认识了一个人。
What's his story? He's silly.
他怎么样？他很傻。
Goofy but cute.
傻乎乎的但很可爱。
What's his name? His name?
他叫什么名字？他的名字？
Um, his name is Joey...
嗯，他叫乔伊…
Van Helsing.
范海辛。
What?
什么？
I'm sure it's a coincidence. It's a common name.
我肯定这只是巧合。这是个常见的名字。
And you didn't hit it off with Timmy Hitler?
那你怎么没和蒂米·希特勒好上？
Very funny.
很好笑。
I don't like it.
我不喜欢。
I can take care of myself.
我能照顾好自己。
Guess what Joey wants to do this weekend?
猜猜乔伊这周末想干什么？
Behead you? Ha-ha.
砍掉你的头？哈哈。
I need to see my wife's chart.
我需要看我妻子的病历。
You know, I've asked about four times in the past hour.
你知道，过去一小时里我已经问了四次了。
So get me the goddamn chart.
所以把那该死的病历给我。
And don't start with the shifts.
别跟我提轮班的事。
And you won't be sued for malpractice
如果你现在就做，
if you do it now.
就不会因为医疗事故被起诉。
Hell no, we won't go.
地狱不，我们不去。
Hell no--
地狱不——
Enough already. I've had enough.
够了。我已经受够了。
Hi, honey. Hi, honey.
嗨，亲爱的。嗨，亲爱的。
Love you.
爱你。
I told them not to bring you any-- look at this.
我告诉过他们不要给你带任何——看这个。
I don't want you to eat this. Look at this.
我不想让你吃这个。看这个。
They use this for breast implants in the other wing.
他们在另一个病区用这个做隆胸手术。
Guess where I went? Cappuccino.
猜猜我去了哪里？卡布奇诺。
Oh-- Look at this.
哦——看这个。
How much? How much do we love cannoli?
我们有多爱奶油卷？
All right, maybe later.
好吧，也许晚点再说。
How you doing in there?
你在里面怎么样？
Ugh.
呃。
I'm tired. Oh, shit.
我累了。哦，该死。
You got jury duty. What?
你收到陪审团通知了。什么？
8:00 a.m. No.
早上8点。不。
How could this happen?
这怎么可能发生？
We're paid in cash. We don't do taxes.
我们收的是现金。我们不交税。
I don't even have a driver's license.
我甚至没有驾照。
Our credit cards are through a third party.
我们的信用卡是通过第三方办理的。
Oh. I voted once.
哦。我投过一次票。
You what? I voted for Dukakis.
你什么？我投了杜卡基斯。
Dukakis? It was before I turned.
杜卡基斯？那是我转化之前。
And I was just thinking about the good of the country.
我当时只是在考虑国家的利益。
Country? It's just business.
国家？那只是生意。
From the Dutch West India Company
从荷兰西印度公司
to the slave trade.
到奴隶贸易。
How do you know all this stuff?
你怎么知道所有这些东西？
Um, The History Channel.
嗯，历史频道。
Yay!
耶！
If you're here and he's there, why don't you talk?
如果你在这儿而他在那儿，为什么你们不说话？
Nobody talks.
没人说话。
Do you want him to think I'm 40?
你想让他以为我40岁吗？
So, if the city has too much garbage,
所以，如果城市垃圾太多，
and rats eat garbage,
而老鼠吃垃圾，
why don't we just get rats to eat the garbage
为什么我们不直接让老鼠吃垃圾
instead of spraying toxic crap everywhere?
而不是到处喷洒有毒的垃圾？
Rats breed too quickly. So?
老鼠繁殖太快了。所以呢？
What if we give them birth control?
如果我们给它们节育呢？
You mean get rats to put on condoms?
你是说让老鼠戴上避孕套？
Yeah. Teensy-weensy little condoms.
是的。超小超小的避孕套。
Who's that old hippie talking to Fred?
那个和弗雷德说话的老嬉皮士是谁？
You must mean the girls from the graveyard shift.
你肯定是指墓地班的女孩们。
Shit. I used to go out with him
该死。我以前和他约会过
before you and I knew each other.
在你我认识之前。
Oh, my God. He's gonna expect you to be like 40.
哦，我的天。他会以为你大概40岁了。
I know. Hi.
我知道。嗨。
Wow.
哇哦。
How is it possible?
这怎么可能？
How is what possible?
什么怎么可能？
Goody, you have not aged a day.
古蒂，你一天都没老。
Mister, my name is Susan.
先生，我叫苏珊。
But my mother's name was Goody. Did you know her?
但我妈妈的名字是古蒂。你认识她吗？
Goody Rutherford? Is that your mother?
古蒂·卢瑟福？那是你妈妈？
Yes, but she passed away.
是的，但她去世了。
Oh. I-I-I'm sorry.
哦。我-我-我很抱歉。
My name is Danny Horowitz.
我叫丹尼·霍洛维茨。
Did she ever, uh, you know, like, mention me?
她有没有，呃，你知道，像，提起过我？
I think.
我想。
But we have to get to work. Hey.
但我们得去上班了。嘿。
Hi, I under-- listen. I have to talk to you.
嗨，我明白——听着。我必须和你谈谈。
Please call me tomorrow.
请明天打电话给我。
Okay. Tomorrow night.
好的。明晚。
Night, of course.
晚上，当然。
Just like your mother.
就像你妈妈一样。
Okay.
好的。
So, is this your place? It's my parents' place.
那么，这是你的地方吗？这是我父母的地方。
When my ex and I broke up, I was traveling
当我和前任分手时，我在旅行
and I haven't found a new place yet.
还没找到新地方。
Iris recognition. So, what does your dad do?
虹膜识别。那么，你爸爸是做什么的？
Well, he works for Homeland Security now,
嗯，他现在为国土安全部工作，
but he was with MI-6 in London for quite a long time.
但他曾在伦敦的军情六处工作了很长时间。
So is he, um, some kind of spy?
那么他是，嗯，某种间谍？
Yeah, like James Bond but shorter.
是的，像詹姆斯·邦德但矮一点。
Listen, Stacy. There's something I have to tell you.
听着，斯泰茜。有件事我必须告诉你。
What? I'm older than you think.
什么？我比你想象的要老。
I've been helping my dad with this project for a few years,
我帮我爸爸做这个项目已经几年了，
and since I'm still in school, you probably think I'm, like, 20.
既然我还在上学，你可能觉得我大概20岁。
But I'm almost 25.
但我快25岁了。
And since you're like 17--
而你大概17岁——
Um, actually I'm a little bit older
嗯，其实我也比
than the other kids, too.
其他孩子大一点。
You are?
你是？
Well, great. Well, how old are you?
嗯，太好了。嗯，你多大了？
You don't ask a lady her age.
你不能问女士的年龄。
Well, why not? Because it's very impolite.
嗯，为什么不？因为那非常不礼貌。
How am I gonna find out? I don't know.
我怎么能知道呢？我不知道。
I'm gonna nick your passport.
我要偷你的护照。
I'm never going again. The performance was ghastly.
我再也不去了。表演糟透了。
No, the clown was so--
不，那个小丑太——
Joey. Oh.
乔伊。哦。
I didn't know you had company.
我不知道你有客人。
We just got back. This is Stacy.
我们刚回来。这是斯泰茜。
Stacy, my mother and father.
斯泰茜，我妈妈和爸爸。
Hi, Stacy. Oh, pleasure.
嗨，斯泰茜。哦，荣幸。
Nice to meet you. Uh, yeah.
很高兴见到你。呃，是的。
How do you do? Hi.
你好吗？嗨。
Well, I actually have to get to my job.
嗯，其实我得去上班了。
You work at night?
你晚上工作？
Yeah, it's so depressing.
是的，太令人沮丧了。
But, you know, just until school gets out.
但是，你知道，只是直到学校放假。
I have to go. I'll see you out.
我得走了。我送你出去。
Ta! Yeah.
再见！是的。
Did you feel her hands? Freezing.
你感觉到她的手了吗？冰冷。
I'm glad you're interested. Are you a registered voter?
很高兴你感兴趣。你是注册选民吗？
No matter what's going on in the world,
无论世界上发生了什么，
there's always someone protesting or petitioning,
总有人在抗议或请愿，
and they always wind up in Union Square.
他们最终总是会来到联合广场。
Even in the 1840s, people were pamphleteering for abolition.
即使在1840年代，人们也在散发传单要求废除奴隶制。
...southern flesh peddlers!
…南方的肉贩子！
Slavery will tear our country apart!
奴隶制将撕裂我们的国家！
Sir, may I proffer you a pamphlet?
先生，我可以递给你一本小册子吗？
Abolition now!
立即废奴！
Sir-- sir, may I proffer you a pamphlet?
先生——先生，我可以递给你一本小册子吗？
And in the 1950s,
而在1950年代，
thousands of people protested to stop
成千上万的人抗议阻止
the execution of the Rosenbergs.
处决罗森堡夫妇。
Of course, in the '60s, there was always a Vietnam demonstration.
当然，在60年代，总是有越南示威。
Hell no, we won't go!
地狱不，我们不去！
Hell no, we won't go! Hell no...
地狱不，我们不去！地狱不…
Must've been pretty crazy to see your old boyfriend like that, huh?
看到你的老男友那样一定很疯狂吧，嗯？
How long were you guys together?
你们在一起多久了？
Over a year. We never lived together,
一年多。我们从未同居过，
but we saw each other every night.
但我们每晚都见面。
I forgot how nice it felt seeing someone you love all the time.
我忘了那种一直见到你爱的人的感觉有多好。
I wonder what Joey's parents think about me.
我想知道乔伊的父母对我是怎么想的。
So what did you think of Stacy?
那么你觉得斯泰茜怎么样？
She's rather pale.
她相当苍白。
How do you mean?
你是什么意思？
What your mother means is she's...
你妈妈的意思是她是…
exceedingly white.
异常地白。
So you don't like her because of the color of her skin?
所以你不喜欢她是因为她的肤色？
Is that what you're telling me?
你是在告诉我这个吗？
Oh, don't be so dramatic.
哦，别这么戏剧化。
No, it's simply that she's not like us.
不，只是因为她不像我们。
You mean wealthy, over-educated,
你是说富有，受过度教育，
Upper-West-Side, paranoid, ghoul-chasing--
上西区，偏执，追逐食尸鬼——
Oh, for fuck's sake. She's undead!
哦，看在老天的份上。她是不死的！
And I forbid you to see her!
我禁止你见她！
You think everyone is a vampire.
你以为每个人都是吸血鬼。
Just because somebody stays up late,
就因为有人熬夜，
doesn't go to bed before 3:00...
3点前不上床…
Well excuse me for being overly vigilant.
好吧，原谅我过度警惕。
...doesn't mean hey can just grow fangs,
…不意味着他们就能长出獠牙，
put on a black cape... But I think beings
穿上黑斗篷… 但我认为那些
devoid of warm blood... ...and fly around tow like a bat!
缺乏温暖血液的生物… …像蝙蝠一样在城里飞来飞去！
Just because they're a little peaky,
就因为他们有点苍白，
it doesn't mean they drink blood.
不意味着他们喝血。
...roam the street at night looking for innocent victims.
…晚上在街上游荡寻找无辜的受害者。
You are so intolerant.
你太不宽容了。
Enough! Stop it, both of you.
够了！停下，你们俩。
Let's just invite your little friend to supper.
我们邀请你的小朋友来吃晚饭吧。
If she's one of them, we'll know.
如果她是他们中的一员，我们就会知道。
Fine.
好的。
Tonight, we're meeting under sad circumstances.
今晚，我们是在悲伤的情况下相聚的。
I'm sure by now you've all heard about David's
我相信现在你们都听说过大卫的
tragic Daylight Savings accident.
悲惨的夏令时事故了。
Boy, one century you're here
天哪，一个世纪你还在这里
and the next you're gone.
下一个世纪你就消失了。
Do you sense something gross?
你感觉到什么恶心的东西了吗？
Yes.
是的。
I see we have a newcomer.
我看到我们有个新人。
Uh, yeah, hi. I'm Rita.
呃，是的，嗨。我是丽塔。
Hi, Rita.
嗨，丽塔。
I am a psy-vampire.
我是个精神吸血鬼。
What exactly is that? Psychic vampire.
那到底是什么？精神吸血鬼。
I'm able to feed off other people's auras.
我能够吸食别人的气场。
You know, I absorb their energy.
你知道，我吸收他们的能量。
How do you know you're not just annoying them?
你怎么知道你不是在烦他们？
Psy-vampires are a true vampiric subset, okay?
精神吸血鬼是一个真正的吸血鬼亚种，好吗？
And we don't need blood to draw--
而且我们不需要血液来吸取——
What the fuck is that?
那他妈的是什么？
All right, all right. Settle down.
好了，好了。安静下来。
We really gotta be more careful
我们真的要更小心
about how we announce our meetings.
我们宣布会议的方式。
Anybody else have something to share?
还有人有什么要分享的吗？
Stacy got called in for jury duty,
斯泰茜被叫去当陪审员了，
but she hasn't voted since the '80s.
但她自从80年代就没投过票了。
That happened to me.
我也遇到过这种事。
And they're bringing me in for an audit.
他们要对我进行审计。
Everybody call on your stems
每个人都联系你们的源头
and any human-feeders you know.
以及任何你们认识的吸食人血者。
But how are we gonna find Cisserus?
但我们怎么找到西瑟勒斯？
You don't know her resting place?
你不知道她的安息之地？
When she wants us, she summons us.
当她想要我们时，她会召唤我们。
We never call on her.
我们从不主动联系她。
Okay.
好的。
We all gotta work together, folks.
我们都得一起努力，各位。
The community is being persecuted.
社区正在遭受迫害。
I've seen it all before.
我以前见过这一切。
Now instead of tortures, they're using computers.
现在他们不用酷刑了，他们在用电脑。
Does Mr. Davidoff know you are coming?
达维多夫先生知道你们要来吗？
Mr. Davidoff is aware
达维多夫先生知道
we'll be here between 7:00 a.m. and 12:00 p.m.
我们会在早上7点到中午12点之间来。
But don't you need a search warrant?
但你们不需要搜查令吗？
Madam, you've insultingly confused us with the police.
女士，你侮辱性地把我们和警察混淆了。
I'm from Time Warner,
我是时代华纳的，
and if you ever want to see Jon Stewart again,
如果你还想再见到乔恩·斯图尔特，
you'll open this door.
你就打开这扇门。
Let's get some light in here.
让我们弄点光进来。
Morning, Sunshine.
早上好，阳光。
Buenas noches, chicas.
晚上好，姑娘们。
Have you seen Ivan?
你们见过伊万吗？
He hasn't answered any of my summonses.
他没回应我任何召唤。
Uh, I think we saw him last week.
呃，我想我们上周见过他。
Something must have happened.
肯定出事了。
He's not strong enough to ignore you.
他不够强大到能无视你。
Well, you chicas will just have to fill in.
嗯，你们姑娘们就得顶上了。
But we're only good at modeling and light clerical work.
但我们只擅长做模特和轻量文书工作。
So, you fold these carefully,
所以，你仔细地把这些叠好，
and you pack this soil.
你把这土装起来。
Don't you just love these "As-seen-on-TV" bags?
难道你不喜欢这些“电视购物”袋子吗？
Look how much soil it can fit.
看它能装多少土。
Oh, it's a good thing we're here because there's gonna be
哦，我们在这儿是件好事，因为会有
a big meeting with all the local stems and ELFs.
一个所有本地源头和ELF的大会。
There's been a lot of persecution of the community.
社区一直受到很多迫害。
What do I care? Well, if you keep acting
我关心什么？嗯，如果你继续这么
so recklessly, they're gonna find you.
鲁莽行事，他们会找到你的。
No one will ever find my lair.
没人会找到我的巢穴。
And I'm in the one place no New Yorker ever goes.
而且我在那个没有纽约人会去的地方。
But your behavior makes it harder for everyone else.
但你的行为让其他人更难。
For who?
为谁？
For Vlad Tepish and his doofus peasants?
为弗拉德·泰皮什和他那些傻瓜农民？
"Vlad the Impaler"?
“穿刺公弗拉德”？
I'll tell you what that whole impaling routine was.
我告诉你那整个穿刺把戏是什么。
Compensation.
补偿。
You know what I'm saying?
你知道我在说什么吗？
Besides, I am leaving town.
再说，我要离开镇子了。
And look at this pimpin' travel coffin he made me.
看看他给我做的这个时髦旅行棺材。
Here's the itinerary.
这是行程安排。
Just get me on cargo before dawn.
黎明前把我弄上货运就行了。
It's a private jet.
这是私人飞机。
Spain? What's in Spain?
西班牙？西班牙有什么？
It is not just the rain in Spain.
不仅仅是西班牙的雨。
Look at him.
看看他。
Diego Bardem.
迭戈·巴登。
Only the handsomest, most talented man in the world.
世界上最英俊、最有才华的男人。
Do you know him? No, I don't know him.
你认识他吗？不，我不认识他。
But I got mad love for him.
但我对他很有爱。
And I'll tell you a secret.
我告诉你一个秘密。
I am not gonna use any hypnotism.
我不会使用任何催眠术。
I want this to be real.
我希望这是真的。
I haven't felt this way about anyone since Al Jolson.
自从阿尔·乔尔森之后，我再没对任何人有过这种感觉。
The Mammy guy?
那个演《黑人妈妈》的家伙？
Yes, the Mammy guy.
是的，那个演《黑人妈妈》的家伙。
I mean, he was an amazingly dynamic performer.
我的意思是，他是个极其有活力的表演者。
You have no idea because you never saw him live.
你根本不知道，因为你从未见过他的现场表演。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
哎，哎，哎，哎，哎。
Hey.
嘿。
What did your parents say about me?
你父母对我是怎么说的？
Are you near your computer? Yeah.
你在电脑旁边吗？是的。
Come on iChat. I wanna see you.
上iChat吧。我想见你。
Oh!
哦！
I don't-- I don't have iChat.
我不——我没有iChat。
Yeah, you do. It's built in.
是的，你有。它是内置的。
Yeah, but my roommate was spray painting
是的，但我的室友在喷漆
and she got paint on the lens.
她把油漆弄到镜头上了。
So... Pfft.
所以… 噗。
What did your parents say?
你父母说了什么？
They thought you were a bit pale.
他们觉得你有点苍白。
What do you mean pale?
你是什么意思苍白？
Well, you know, pale, fair skin.
嗯，你知道，苍白，皮肤白皙。
Like maybe you were sick or something.
像是你可能生病了或者别的什么。
Well, it's just those environmental light bulbs.
嗯，只是那些环保灯泡。
I mean, they make everybody look horrible.
我的意思是，它们让每个人看起来都很可怕。
Look, they want you to come for dinner on Friday.
听着，他们想让你周五来吃晚饭。
Can you make it?
你能来吗？
Oh, I'll be there.
哦，我会去的。
Stay still.
保持静止。
It's good, right? I think it's totally working.
很好，对吧？我觉得完全奏效了。
I'm gonna be so tan.
我会晒得很黑。
Hi.
嗨。
Wow. You look...
哇哦。你看起来…
Robust?
健壮？
Sure.
当然。
Come in. Dinner will be a few minutes.
请进。晚餐还要几分钟。
Let me give you the tour.
我带你参观一下。
What is all this stuff?
这些都是什么东西？
Well, it's mostly stuff from my grandfather
嗯，大部分是我祖父
or my great grandfather.
或我曾祖父的东西。
My father is an expert on vampirism.
我父亲是吸血鬼方面的专家。
Told you my family's nuts.
告诉过你我家很疯。
What's this thing? Ah, well...
这是什么东西？啊，嗯…
if someone you suspect of being a vampire dies,
如果你怀疑某人是吸血鬼并且他死了，
you place this over their neck before they're buried
你在他被埋葬前把这个放在他的脖子上
and if they wake up and try to climb out of their coffin,
如果他醒来并试图爬出他的棺材，
they get beheaded.
他就会被砍头。
Dinner's ready!
晚餐准备好了！
Hey, I know him.
嘿，我认识他。
You know him?
你认识他？
I mean, I know who he is.
我的意思是，我知道他是谁。
It's Vlad Tepish.
是弗拉德·泰皮什。
It's pronounced "Tee-pees."
发音是“Tee-pees”。
He was one of the most sadistic figures in history.
他是历史上最残暴的人物之一。
Well, I guess that sort of depends on your point of view.
嗯，我想这某种程度上取决于你的观点。
Really?
真的吗？
How many points of view can there be on the subject
关于穿刺人和饮用他们血液这个主题
of impaling people and drinking their blood?
能有多少种观点？
If a weird stunt like that stops
如果那样一个怪异的噱头阻止了
the entire Ottoman Empire from taking over Europe.
整个奥斯曼帝国接管欧洲。
His armor is in the museum in Bucharest.
他的盔甲在布加勒斯特的博物馆里。
I mean, they consider him a hero.
我的意思是，他们认为他是英雄。
Yeah, if it wasn't for him, we'd all be speaking "Ottomanese."
是的，如果不是他，我们现在都会说“奥斯曼语”。
Didn't you like your fish?
你不喜欢你的鱼吗？
Shall we make something else for you?
要不要我们给你做点别的？
Oh, no, thank you, Mrs. Van Helsing.
哦，不，谢谢你，范海辛夫人。
I'm enjoying my dinner a great deal.
我非常享受我的晚餐。
Now, you must try our soup.
现在，你必须尝尝我们的汤。
It's an old Van Helsing recipe.
这是一个古老的范海辛食谱。
Ahh!
啊！
Not a fan of garlic?
不喜欢大蒜？
Oh, no, it's not the garlic. It's the salt.
哦，不，不是大蒜。是盐。
Even the tiniest bit and I blow up
哪怕是最微小的一点，我都会膨胀
like a Thanksgiving Day balloon.
得像个感恩节气球。
My father thinks that if he gives us garlic breath,
我父亲认为如果他让我们有大蒜口气，
we won't make out.
我们就不会亲热了。
Not going to work, Pops.
行不通的，老爸。
Ma, we'll take dessert later. The movie starts at 9:30.
妈，我们晚点再吃甜点。电影9:30开始。
I'll just get our things.
我去拿我们的东西。
Hmm.
嗯。
You have a very strong will, Dr. Van Helsing.
你的意志力很强，范海辛医生。
What are your intentions with my son?
你对我儿子有什么意图？
What do you mean?
你是什么意思？
Do you plan to suck the life out of him?
你打算吸干他的生命吗？
No more than any other girlfriend.
不比任何其他女朋友多。
Hey, you ready?
嘿，你准备好了吗？
Thank you for dinner.
谢谢你的晚餐。
See you later.
待会儿见。
Oh, I know. But did you see the girl
哦，我知道。但是你看到那个女孩
who left with Joey? Is she one of them?
和乔伊一起离开了吗？她是他们中的一员吗？
I wasn't really paying attention.
我没怎么注意。
That girl, she seemed pretty dark.
那个女孩，她看起来挺阴暗的。
But it's all gonna be on my phone.
但这都会在我的手机上。
So hold on.
所以等等。
Wait, I don't remember seeing empty chairs.
等等，我不记得看到空椅子。
What did I do wrong?
我做错了什么？
You didn't do anything wrong.
你没做错任何事。
Why do people bother going out
为什么人们还要费劲出去
if the only thing they want to bond with
如果他们唯一想联系的
is their little glowing boxes?
是他们那些发光的小盒子？
Don't go grandma on me.
别对我摆老奶奶架子。
Oh, there's Renfield. Hey.
哦，伦菲尔德在那儿。嘿。
Uh, you guys, um...
呃，你们，嗯…
kinda can't sit here unless we order a $400 bottle.
有点不能坐这儿，除非我们点一瓶400美元的酒。
- Don't worry about it.
- Bottle service.
- 别担心。
- 包厢服务。
She left him 10 minutes ago. The sex must be great.
她10分钟前离开了他。性生活一定很棒。
Oh, we haven't done it yet.
哦，我们还没做呢。
Oh, so it's a purely textual relationship?
哦，所以这纯粹是文字关系？
I've been looking for you, you lifeless bitch.
我一直在找你，你这个没生命的婊子。
What is your problem?
你有什么毛病？
What did you do to Ivan?
你对伊万做了什么？
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
First you kill my game with Juicy girl.
首先你破坏了我和Juicy女孩的好事。
Now Ivan is missing.
现在伊万失踪了。
Suckerin' succotash.
倒霉透顶。
Guys, guys, guys!
伙计们，伙计们，伙计们！
Not in front of the day players.
别在凡人面前。
The past few minutes, you remember nothing.
过去几分钟，你什么都不记得。
Complete Sergeant Schultz.
完全像舒尔茨中士。
I know nothing!
我什么都不知道！
I saw nothing! Now cut it out.
我什么都没看见！现在住手。
Besides, why would we hurt Ivan?
再说，我们为什么要伤害伊万？
We'd just wind up doing more work for Cisserus.
我们只会为西瑟勒斯做更多的工作。
Actually, it's a good thing we ran into you.
其实，遇到你真是件好事。
We need you to come to a Sanguines Anonymous meeting.
我们需要你来参加嗜血者互诫协会的会议。
No way. You don't have to join,
没门。你不用加入，
but a lot of weird stuff has been going down.
但发生了很多奇怪的事情。
They're trying to force us out into the sun.
他们想把我们逼到阳光下。
You think this has something to do with Ivan's disappearance?
你认为这和伊万的失踪有关吗？
It might.
也许吧。
Did anyone in his building see anything?
他楼里有人看到什么了吗？
The neighbor said the cable company was there.
邻居说有线电视公司的人来过。
Can Time Warner just burst into a person's home and kill them?
时代华纳能就这么闯入别人家然后杀了他们吗？
Yeah, they're terrible.
是的，他们很可怕。
Come to a meeting. We've got to figure this out.
来参加会议。我们必须弄清楚这件事。
Everybody's getting audited.
每个人都在被审计。
Well, you don't have to go.
嗯，你不用去。
What?
什么？
An audit is just the IRS saying,
审计只是国税局说，
"We think you should pay more taxes."
“我们认为你应该交更多的税。”
And if you agree with them, then you say, "Okay, how much?"
如果你同意他们，那么你说，“好的，多少？”
But you only have to go in if you wanna challenge them.
但你只有在想挑战他们的时候才需要去。
How do you know this?
你怎么知道这个？
I'm a CPA.
我是注册会计师。
You are? Yeah.
你是？是的。
You just got some new clients.
你刚得到了一些新客户。
Not me. I have a guy.
不是我。我有个人。
What are you wearing?
你穿的什么？
It's like the history of fashion.
这就像时尚史。
I'm going to see Danny. I wanna look nice.
我要去见丹尼。我想看起来漂亮点。
Gibson Girl shirts were the prettiest.
吉布森女孩衬衫是最漂亮的。
1960s skirts are great on short women.
1960年代的裙子对矮个子女人来说很棒。
1970s shoes make you tall but are comfortable.
1970年代的鞋子让你显高但很舒服。
Okay, but what's with the hat?
好吧，但那帽子是怎么回事？
It's a boater.
这是平顶草帽。
People always said it looked spiffy on me.
人们总说它戴在我身上很时髦。
People from your barbershop quartet
是你理发店四重唱的人们
or people from the Republican convention?
还是共和党大会的人们？
Oh, God.
哦，天哪。
Here we are.
我们到了。
"Architectural Digest" time. Enjoy yourself.
《建筑文摘》时间。尽情享受吧。
Sure you don't want anything to drink?
你确定不要喝点什么吗？
I'm sure. Well, I'm not.
我确定。嗯，我不确定。
I need some coffee, man. For energy.
我需要点咖啡，伙计。为了能量。
I just made this last week.
我上周刚做了这个。
Oh. You work for the government?
哦。你为政府工作？
Do I look like I work for the government?
我看起来像为政府工作的吗？
I'm with the ACLU.
我是美国公民自由联盟的。
Right now I'm in the middle of this deportation case
现在我正在处理这个驱逐出境的案子
with abuses of wiretapping. It's unbearable.
涉及滥用窃听。这令人无法忍受。
Well, I thought if the government
嗯，我以为如果政府
doesn't hear terrorist-related stuff,
没听到与恐怖分子相关的东西，
they have to hang up.
他们就必须挂断。
No.
不。
Ah, look at this.
啊，看这个。
I was going through these looking for your mother.
我翻这些是为了找你妈妈。
Look at these.
看这些。
She had this habit of just
她有这个习惯，就是
ducking out right before they took a picture.
在他们拍照前就躲开。
Well, she was superstitious.
嗯，她很迷信。
Still, I mean, it's a little nutty, isn't it?
不过，我的意思是，这有点疯狂，不是吗？
My God.
我的天。
I have this one. You do? Really?
我有这张。你有？真的吗？
She saved it?
她保存了它？
You better put yours in plastic.
你最好把你的放进塑料袋里。
She liked this, huh? Well, why not?
她喜欢这个，嗯？嗯，为什么不呢？
I was not bad-looking back then, huh?
我那时长得不赖，嗯？
What an amazing time this was.
那真是个了不起的时代。
Being young and in love.
年轻并坠入爱河。
Feeling like you're a part of something that really mattered.
感觉自己是真正重要的事情的一部分。
Your mother never mentioned why she just disappeared?
你妈妈从没提过她为什么就消失了？
Not really. Oh, man.
不完全是。哦，天哪。
Hey, you know what?
嘿，你知道吗？
I have to get movies for my wife before the store closes.
我得在商店关门前给我妻子买电影。
Right on. Huh?
好吧。嗯？
My way.
我的方式。
I'll go with. Oh.
我跟你一起去。哦。
All right, cool.
好吧，酷。
You know, Angela is really in and out.
你知道，安吉拉真的是时好时坏。
And that's why I gotta get her movies that she really loves.
所以我得给她买她真正喜欢的电影。
So, you know, when she dozes off,
所以，你知道，当她打瞌睡时，
you know, she won't miss anything, really.
你知道，她不会错过任何东西，真的。
Can I help? Uh, no.
我能帮忙吗？呃，不。
When I see 'em, I'll know it.
当我看到它们时，我就会知道。
Then I'm gonna look around. Okay, cool.
那我要四处看看。好的，酷。
Excuse me.
失陪一下。
Do you have any James Cagney posters?
你们有詹姆斯·卡格尼的海报吗？
Oh, James Cameron?
哦，詹姆斯·卡梅隆？
No, uh, James Cagney.
不，呃，詹姆斯·卡格尼。
You know, "Made it, Ma! Top of the world!"
你知道，“成功了，妈！世界之巅！”
No.
不。
What about...
那…
Fred Astaire? No.
弗雷德·阿斯泰尔？不。
Jack Lemmon? No.
杰克·莱蒙？不。
Paul Newman. Oh, the salad dressing guy?
保罗·纽曼。哦，那个沙拉酱家伙？
Yeah. No.
是的。不。
Phones on the ground.
手机放地上。
Phones on the ground now. Drop 'em!
手机现在放地上。放下！
Hands in the air. Hands in the air. Give me the money.
手举起来。手举起来。把钱给我。
Don't you point that. He's got a heart condition.
别指着那个。他有心脏病。
Shut up! Oh, my God!
闭嘴！哦，我的天！
Fuck. Come on!
操。快点！
He's having a heart attack. No, no, no, lady.
他心脏病发作了。不，不，不，女士。
Get up and give me the money now.
起来把钱给我，现在。
Shit, come on! Oh!
该死，快点！哦！
Stop it.
住手。
Calm down.
冷静下来。
Mm. Feel better?
嗯。感觉好点了吗？
Yeah.
是的。
You are gonna take this couple to the hospital.
你要把这对夫妇送到医院。
And no more stealing.
别再偷东西了。
The bite was from your cat.
咬伤是你的猫造成的。
You guys, take CPR courses.
你们，去上CPR课程。
You hate junk food.
你讨厌垃圾食品。
And get "Public Enemy."
去买《人民公敌》。
The Cagney one.
卡格尼演的那部。
You all right?
你还好吗？
I could hypnotize you,
我可以催眠你，
but I've been wanting to tell you.
但我一直想告诉你。
So what are you saying? You broke up with me 'cause
所以你是说？你跟我分手是因为
you wouldn't drink my blood? Is that what you're telling me?
你不想喝我的血？你是在告诉我这个吗？
I don't drink human blood.
我不喝人血。
You don't? That guy, what was that?
你不喝？那个人，那是什么？
No. Have you ever seen a vampire bat?
不。你见过吸血蝙蝠吗？
A little rodent can get the blood out of an entire cow
一只小啮齿动物能从一整头牛身上吸干血
in a few minutes because of this enzyme in their saliva.
在几分钟内，因为它们唾液中的这种酶。
It's a completely safe blood thinner.
它是一种完全安全的血液稀释剂。
And I also have it.
我也有。
I didn't drink that man's blood.
我没喝那个人的血。
I spit into him to stop the stroke.
我往他身上吐口水是为了阻止中风。
Oh. You just spit into him.
哦。你只是往他身上吐口水。
Oh, that's a whole other ball game.
哦，那完全是另一回事了。
Well, if I didn't, he would have had a lot of brain damage.
嗯，如果我不那么做，他会有严重的脑损伤。
How old are you?
你多大了？
A little older than you.
比你大一点。
So people can only be around you for, like, what--
所以人们只能在你身边待，比如，什么——
a year or something?
一年左右？
No, I could go around seven years
不，我可以待七年左右
without them expecting me to look older.
而不让他们期望我看起来变老。
And I would've stayed with you for as long as possible.
我会尽可能长时间地和你在一起。
But when you became one of the student leaders,
但当你成为学生领袖之一时，
people on the street recognized you.
街上的人都认出你了。
I thought, "This is his time."
我想，“这是他的时代。”
You could have your choice of any woman out there.
你可以选择任何外面的女人。
It didn't seem right to rob you of the chance
剥夺你遇见某个了不起的人的机会
to meet someone amazing.
似乎是不对的。
And you did, didn't you?
你确实遇到了，不是吗？
I did. I really did.
是的。我确实遇到了。
And you know what? I really should check
你知道吗？我真的应该查查
and see how she's doing.
看看她怎么样了。
And I gotta tell you something else.
我还要告诉你别的事。
I feel like I'm really, like, tripping right now.
我觉得我现在真的，像是，有点懵。
Am I gonna see you again?
我还会再见到你吗？
Uh...
呃…
of course, yeah.
当然，是的。
Okay, this is Germany before World War II.
好的，这是二战前的德国。
The sleepwalker keeps murdering people,
梦游者不停地杀人，
but only because the evil guy has him under a spell.
但这只是因为那个邪恶的家伙用咒语控制了他。
What does that remind you of?
这让你想起了什么？
I'm flummoxed.
我被难住了。
Germany? Evil spell?
德国？邪恶咒语？
Adolf?
阿道夫？
Your eyes remind me of somebody.
你的眼睛让我想起了某个人。
Adolf Hitler.
阿道夫·希特勒。
No, that wasn't who I was thinking of.
不，那不是我想到的人。
Audrey Hepburn. Same initials, though.
奥黛丽·赫本。不过首字母缩写一样。
Can you please just focus on symbolism?
你能请你专注于象征意义吗？
Sorry.
抱歉。
Can I be under your spell?
我能被你的咒语控制吗？
Or better still, you could be under my spell.
或者更好的是，你可以被我的咒语控制。
What are you gonna make me do?
你要让我做什么？
Laugh hysterically.
歇斯底里地大笑。
Holy shit.
我的天。
Has it ever been like that for your before?
以前有过这样的感觉吗？
Not since the '80s.
80年代以后就没这样了。
Hey, where are you going?
嘿，你去哪儿？
Um, I've got an early class.
嗯，我有个早课。
Well, ditch it and come back to bed.
嗯，翘掉它回床上吧。
I can't. But I'll call you later.
我不能。但我晚点会给你打电话。
Come on, my parents won't be home until tomorrow.
来吧，我父母明天才回家。
Look, it's a little early in the relationship to get into this,
听着，现在谈这个关系有点早，
but I've really gotta go.
但我真的得走了。
What the--
什么——
Something bothering you? What?
有什么困扰你吗？什么？
No.
不。
If there's anything you wanna talk about...
如果你有什么想谈的…
maybe trouble with Stacy, or...
也许是和斯泰茜的麻烦，或者…
Yeah, 'cause you'd love that.
是啊，因为你会喜欢那样。
He's not answering my texts, my tweets, my e-mails,
他不回我的短信，我的推特，我的邮件，
my voicemail, my Facebook messages--
我的语音留言，我的脸书消息——
Do you think he'll tell his father?
你觉得他会告诉他父亲吗？
No, he wouldn't do that. What about Danny?
不，他不会那么做。那丹尼呢？
Do you think he'll tell the authorities?
你觉得他会告诉当局吗？
He'd never. How do you know?
他绝不会。你怎么知道？
Danny hates authority.
丹尼讨厌权威。
I'm gonna go to his class so he has to confront me.
我要去他的课上，这样他就必须面对我。
Are you mad at me?
你生我的气了吗？
Don't go away. Huh? What?
别走开。嗯？什么？
Really? Yeah.
真的吗？是的。
How do you like them apples?
你觉得这些苹果怎么样？
Garlic?
大蒜？
You were afraid of it the other night.
你那天晚上怕它。
Yeah, because I've always hated garlic.
是的，因为我一直讨厌大蒜。
Can we please just talk about this?
我们能请你谈谈这个吗？
My father tried to warn me. Against what?
我父亲试图警告我。反对什么？
I have never harmed a human being or a domestic animal
我从未伤害过一个人或一只家畜
my entire life.
在我一生中。
Oh, so you didn't go after me 'cause I'm a Van Helsing?
哦，所以你没追我因为我是范海辛？
No. If anything, I would've stayed away.
不。如果有什么的话，我会避开。
Besides, if I wanted to drink your blood,
再说，如果我想喝你的血，
would I have written you this 10-page report
我会给你写这篇10页的报告
on Freud and his influence on surrealist imagery?
关于弗洛伊德和他对超现实主义意象的影响吗？
How do I know you wrote this for me?
我怎么知道你这是为我写的？
Because I also wrote one on World War I
因为我还写了一篇关于第一次世界大战
and how it gave birth to Surrealism.
以及它如何催生了超现实主义。
Actually, I like that one better.
其实，我更喜欢那篇。
Oh, you do?
哦，你喜欢？
So now you trust me, huh?
所以现在你信任我了，嗯？
I trust you to give yourself the better grade.
我相信你会给自己打更高的分数。
I don't blame you.
我不怪你。
You know I would never hurt you, right?
你知道我永远不会伤害你，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Well, then what is it? Is it the day thing?
嗯，那是什么？是白天的事吗？
Do you want to have a girlfriend
你想要一个女朋友
you can go hiking with and go to the beach?
可以一起去远足和去海滩吗？
No, I'm-- I'm more of a night person.
不，我——我更像个夜猫子。
Is it the blood, then?
那是血的事吗？
You wanna try new restaurants? No, I'm not much of a foodie.
你想尝试新餐馆吗？不，我不太是个吃货。
So what is it?
那是什么？
I hate it when my parents are right.
我讨厌我父母是对的。
Okay, now open.
好的，现在张开。
Thank you!
谢谢你！
You know what? I'm sorry. No, no, no, no.
你知道吗？我很抱歉。不，不，不，不。
I shouldn't be dumping all this on you.
我不该把这些都推给你。
Fine. Yay!
好的。耶！
Come on, just sign the petition.
来吧，就在请愿书上签名。
Okay. Okay.
好的。好的。
Here you go. Right there.
给你。就在这儿。
Ooh.
哦。
Hey, Renfield. Come on in. Hey. How are you, Goody?
嘿，伦菲尔德。进来吧。嘿。你好吗，古蒂？
Jesus.
耶稣。
Hey, Renfield. Hey, how are you?
嘿，伦菲尔德。嘿，你好吗？
Do you mind if I smoke? Yes.
你介意我抽烟吗？是的。
But-- I mean, this can't bother you.
但是——我的意思是，这不会打扰你。
It bothers me if you're hurting yourself.
如果你在伤害自己，这会打扰我。
Well, then awaken me.
那就唤醒我。
It doesn't work that way.
事情不是那样的。
You're an accountant. Do the math.
你是个会计师。算算吧。
If every infected person
如果每个被感染的人
fed on or infected the rest of the people,
都吸食或感染其他人，
the entire population would've eaten itself off the planet
整个种群会在基督诞生之前
long before Christ was even born.
就把自己吃光了。
Only a stem can turn someone.
只有一个源头能转化某人。
Is that the sweater Tepish knit you?
那是泰皮什给你织的毛衣吗？
Mm-hmm. It would be impolite not to wear it.
嗯哼。不穿它会不礼貌。
And it goes with everything.
而且它和什么都搭。
Wait till you see the one he's making you.
等你看到他给你做的那件。
Okay, people.
好了，各位。
This is an amazing event.
这是一个了不起的事件。
Except for Cisserus, we have all the stems
除了西瑟勒斯，我们有所有的源头
from the tri-state area.
来自三州地区。
Vadim the Russian, Ukrainian.
瓦迪姆，俄罗斯人，乌克兰人。
- Ashwan from Kush.
- Hi, Ashwan.
- 阿什万，来自库什。
- 嗨，阿什万。
- Ghuri, the Turkish stem.
- Hi, Ghuri.
- 古里，土耳其源头。
- 嗨，古里。
Yuppa, yuppa.
是的，是的。
I'd like to start by asking,
我想先问问，
how many of you have gotten subpoenas?
你们中有多少人收到了传票？
Excuse me.
失陪一下。
Why do not we just eat the lawyers?
为什么我们不直接吃了那些律师？
You crazy. We can't eat all the lawyers.
你疯了。我们不能吃掉所有律师。
Why not?
为什么不？
Let's just say eating lawyers is out of the question.
我们就说吃律师是不可能的。
I know you can sense
我知道你能感觉到
that we have day players among us.
我们中间有凡人。
This is my granddaughter, Sarah.
这是我的孙女，莎拉。
Hi, Sarah.
嗨，莎拉。
And this is our friend Renfield.
这是我们的朋友伦菲尔德。
He's a CPA so he can help with the IRS stuff.
他是注册会计师，所以他可以帮忙处理国税局的事。
And I understand we have a lawyer here.
我知道我们这里有个律师。
You absolutely do.
你绝对有。
How you doin'? My name is Danny.
你好吗？我叫丹尼。
Hi, Danny. And I'm from the ACLU.
嗨，丹尼。我是美国公民自由联盟的。
From what I understand, you can't be forced out
据我所知，你们不能被迫在白天出去
during the day and you don't want anyone to molest
你们也不希望任何人骚扰
your resting places.
你们的安息之地。
But the government can enter your home any time they want
但政府可以随时进入你们的家
because of the Patriot Act.
因为爱国者法案。
See what's going down now
看看现在发生了什么
is that all your cell phones and your iPhones
是你们所有的手机和iPhone
and all the computers are helping them find you.
以及所有的电脑都在帮助他们找到你们。
So I urge you not to use any of your electronic devices.
所以我敦促你们不要使用任何你们的电子设备。
How will we do anything?
我们将如何做任何事？
How do we even stay in touch with each other?
我们甚至如何保持联系？
I used to write things down.
我过去常常把事情写下来。
Oh, yeah. Like in a datebook. Right.
哦，是的。像是在日程本里。对。
But I need my computer to tell me sunrise and sunset.
但我需要我的电脑告诉我日出和日落。
Oh, I can tell everyone that on my almanac.
哦，我可以用我的年鉴告诉大家。
Under "Sky Watch," it's got phases of the moon,
在“天空观察”下，它有月相，
high tide, sunrise and sunset, and-- good Lord!
高潮，日出和日落，还有——天哪！
What? What is it?
什么？怎么了？
Total eclipse of the sun in two weeks.
两周后有日全食。
Hold on, hold on.
等等，等等。
2:10 to 3:40.
2:10到3:40。
Too bad that wasn't the exact time of our summons.
太糟糕了，那不是我们传票的确切时间。
If we had face time, we could use hypnotism.
如果我们能面对面，我们可以使用催眠术。
No, why? That wouldn't make any difference.
不，为什么？那不会有任何区别。
Couldn't we just change the times of the appointments?
我们不能直接改变预约时间吗？
Yeah. We could get you completely eliminated
是的。我们可以让你们完全从
from their system. We could delete and change
他们的系统中消失。我们可以删除和更改
everything in their computers.
他们电脑里的一切。
You know, I can see why
你知道，我能理解为什么
you have sworn off human blood.
你们发誓戒除人血了。
Awesome. Do you want to join?
太棒了。你想加入吗？
How would you ladies like to be my wives?
你们女士们愿意做我的妻子吗？
Eat me.
吃我。
All right. Not literally.
好吧。不是字面上的。
Oh, are you okay?
哦，你还好吗？
You were sick yesterday, too.
你昨天也病了。
Look what I got you.
看我给你买了什么。
Pure pharmaceutical grade.
纯医药级。
Oh, but they're so cute.
哦，但它们太可爱了。
They're not like vermin. They could be somebody's pets. Hi!
它们不像害虫。它们可能是某人的宠物。嗨！
I figured they wouldn't make you sick.
我想它们不会让你生病。
It's nothing. I'm fine.
没事。我很好。
It's just when I get up.
只是我起来的时候。
Quit futzing. We have to go.
别瞎忙了。我们得走了。
Oh, don't start with me.
哦，别跟我来这套。
Drop waists are coming back. Yeah, says who?
低腰裙要回来了。是的，谁说的？
I saw a picture of Keira Knightley in one.
我看到一张凯拉·奈特莉穿这种裙子的照片。
Yeah, right.
是的，对。
That's because Keira Knightley's in a movie.
那是因为凯拉·奈特莉在拍电影。
Ha, look at you! I know.
哈，看看你！我知道。
This was my college interview outfit.
这是我大学面试的服装。
Were you trying for a football scholarship?
你是想申请橄榄球奖学金吗？
Ha-ha. It's the only thing I have that looks respectful.
哈哈。这是我唯一看起来体面的衣服。
- Whoa, check it out.
- I know, it's crazy.
- 哇，看那个。
- 我知道，太疯狂了。
Mom, look! I've never seen it before.
妈妈，看！我以前从未见过。
Don't look directly at it, honey.
不要直视它，亲爱的。
Wow, I totally forgot what it was like.
哇，我完全忘了那是什么样子。
It's an entirely different world.
这是一个完全不同的世界。
Oh, so many women.
哦，这么多女人。
Have a nice day.
祝你有个愉快的一天。
Come on, everybody. Let's go. We only have two hours.
来吧，大家。我们走吧。我们只有两个小时。
Hey, so do you know where we're going?
嘿，你知道我们要去哪里吗？
You will do what my accountant says.
你会照我的会计师说的做。
It's CPA.
是注册会计师。
Okay, this is Ghuri.
好的，这是古里。
This is file number 318.
这是档案号318。
This Vlad Tepish.
这是弗拉德·泰皮什。
He was granted asylum in, um...
他被授予庇护在，嗯…
1583.
1583年。
Currently married to a US citizen.
目前与一名美国公民结婚。
Well, four.
嗯，四个。
Yeah, that's okay.
是的，没关系。
Child of an American fiancée.
美国未婚妻的孩子。
For an adjustment of status.
为了调整身份。
A student visa so he can matriculate at UCLA.
学生签证，这样他可以在加州大学洛杉矶分校入学。
Go Bruins.
加油，棕熊队。
Yeah.
是的。
Stacy Daimer is unable to perform jury duty obligations.
斯泰茜·戴默无法履行陪审团义务。
Unable to perform jury duty obligations.
无法履行陪审团义务。
In fact, I'll just delete them. Just delete them.
事实上，我直接删掉它们。直接删掉它们。
Put the deleted names in the trash.
把删除的名字放进垃圾桶。
Deleted names in trash.
删除的名字在垃圾桶里。
Empty the trash. Empty the trash.
清空垃圾桶。清空垃圾桶。
Ask the IT guy to remove the hard drive.
让IT人员移除硬盘。
Go, go, go! Excuse us, coming through!
走，走，走！对不起，借过！
Joey!
乔伊！
Yeah!
耶！
Let me see. Open.
让我看看。张开。
Hold it up. Hold it up.
举起来。举起来。
Aw, beautiful color.
啊，漂亮的颜色。
They're having the book launch party for The Situation
他们正在为《The Situation》举办新书发布派对
right now on 10th. What do you say?
现在就在第十大道。你说呢？
Ugh. Not worth the candle.
呃。不值得费力。
We're happy here.
我们在这里很开心。
Every A-lister in New York will be there.
纽约的每个A级名流都会在那里。
You can have whoever you want.
你可以拥有任何你想要的人。
Mm. You get tired of that.
嗯。你会厌倦那个的。
Oh, I like this song.
哦，我喜欢这首歌。
You wanna dance. Yeah, do you?
你想跳舞。是的，你呢？
Yeah. Okay.
是的。好的。
Aren't you gonna dance?
你不跳舞吗？
Me? I don't think so.
我？我想我不跳。
I'm not very good, no. Yes, you are.
我不太擅长，不。是的，你很擅长。
I remember. Yeah, but I don't remember.
我记得。是的，但我不记得了。
Do you sleep with henchmen?
你和手下睡觉吗？
Joey had to go. His dad is bugging out.
乔伊得走了。他爸爸快抓狂了。
Problems at work, no doubt.
工作上的问题，毫无疑问。
Hmm. Wonder who that could be.
嗯。想知道那会是谁。
Oh, isn't it insane?
哦，这不是很疯狂吗？
I was dating for 25 years
我约会了25年
and I've never imagined to feel this way about somebody.
我从未想象过对某人会有这种感觉。
What about you and Danny?
你和丹尼呢？
Mm, I never stopped loving him.
嗯，我从未停止爱他。
But his wife's sick so there's no even thinking about it.
但他妻子病了，所以甚至不用想了。
I'm just happy around him.
我只是在他身边很开心。
Reminds me of being hopeful.
让我想起了充满希望的感觉。
But how great would it be if we both had relationships?
但如果我们都有了关系那该多好？
I mean, wouldn't it be so cool--
我的意思是，那不是很酷吗——
Mott Street.
莫特街。
Mott Street. Oh!
莫特街。哦！
What is she doing back so soon?
她怎么这么快就回来了？
I guess things didn't work out with Diego.
我想和迭戈的事情没成。
Ugh. She's in Chinatown.
呃。她在唐人街。
God, just when things were going so well.
天哪，就在事情进展得这么顺利的时候。
Mm.
嗯。
Oh-- oh, God.
哦——哦，天哪。
I've never seen real dead people.
我从未见过真正的死人。
What did you do?
你做了什么？
You know how it is
你知道吃中餐是怎么回事
when you eat Chinese.
的时候。
Half an hour later you're hungry again.
半小时后你又饿了。
How could you?
你怎么能？
Oh, I just can't stop eating.
哦，我就是停不下来吃。
I'm so depressed.
我太沮丧了。
Why didn't he like me?
他为什么不喜欢我？
I am so much more bomb-ass than his girlfriend.
我比他女朋友酷多了。
Maybe she wasn't a homicidal maniac.
也许她不是个杀人狂。
Maybe.
也许吧。
This is disgusting!
这太恶心了！
I know.
我知道。
I could so easily hate myself.
我很容易恨自己。
But just because you overdid it one day,
但仅仅因为你有一天过度放纵了，
doesn't mean you have to be bad all weekend.
不意味着你整个周末都必须是坏的。
What's wrong with him?
他怎么了？
Finish him off, will ya?
解决他，好吗？
I said kill him.
我说杀了他。
You really can't kill.
你真的不能杀人。
You guys are so useless.
你们太没用了。
Forget it.
算了。
Hey, can I have a fortune cookie, at least?
嘿，我至少能吃个幸运饼干吗？
That was way too close.
那太接近了。
And I didn't put in rollers.
我还没上卷发器。
I'm gonna have coffin hair tomorrow.
明天我的头发会是棺材头。
I know.
我知道。
Goody, I don't think
古蒂，我觉得
I can do anything like that again.
我再也做不了那样的事了。
Me either.
我也是。
The world changes, we have to adapt.
世界在变，我们必须适应。
These violent old ways
这些暴力的旧方式
don't make any sense anymore.
不再有任何意义了。
But she won't listen.
但她不会听。
She's insane. Oh, tell me about it.
她疯了。哦，跟我说说吧。
Tepish, is there anything like a...
泰皮什，有没有像…
Sanguine's doctor?
嗜血者医生？
Stacy is sick.
斯泰茜病了。
That's impossible. We don't get sick.
那不可能。我们不会生病。
That's what I thought,
我也是这么想的，
but every night when we get up, she vomits.
但每晚我们起来时，她都会呕吐。
Just how old was she when she was awakened?
她被唤醒时到底多大？
20.
20岁。
And I assume there is a boyfriend.
我假设有个男朋友。
Why?
为什么？
She's not sick. She's pregnant.
她没病。她怀孕了。
So she can have a baby?
所以她能生孩子？
No, the pregnancy will end by itself.
不，怀孕会自行结束。
Unless she turns back.
除非她变回去。
Like, if Cisserus dies?
比如，如果西瑟勒斯死了？
Cisserus.
西瑟勒斯。
Don't you worry, hmm?
别担心，嗯？
Stacy will be just fine in about a week.
斯泰茜大约一周后就会没事的。
They notified us about a patient having seizures
他们通知我们一个癫痫发作的病人
who had a double puncture wound. When I asked who checked him in,
身上有双重穿刺伤。当我问是谁给他办理入院时，
I went back to their surveillance cameras.
我回去看了他们的监控录像。
Where's the body? Mount Sinai.
尸体在哪儿？西奈山医院。
Tell them we're coming. Mm-hmm.
告诉他们我们要来了。嗯哼。
All right, sit down, listen to me.
好了，坐下，听我说。
Now, I know you think I'm crazy,
现在，我知道你觉得我疯了，
but you have to do something for me.
但你必须为我做件事。
Sure.
当然。
Carry this with you at all times.
随时带着这个。
What? This is how you load it.
什么？这是装弹的方式。
Only use the silver bullets.
只用银子弹。
Only use them on what? Stacy?
只对什么用？斯泰茜？
Just keep it with you.
就带着它。
Don't give me any shit.
别跟我废话。
When a problem comes along, like hunger, you must whip it.
当问题来临时，比如饥饿，你必须鞭打它。
It says this guy's a comic? He's not even funny.
它说这家伙是个喜剧演员？他一点都不好笑。
I've never seen him in anything.
我从没在任何东西里见过他。
What's on?
放什么呢？
"Assholes Insult People More Talented Than Them."
“混蛋们侮辱比他们更有才华的人。”
"The Excessively '80s Countdown."
“过度80年代倒计时。”
Oh, show Goody.
哦，给古蒂看。
Oh.
哦。
So my father decided to give me this.
所以我父亲决定给我这个。
Hmm. That's weird.
嗯。真奇怪。
Oh, careful. It's got silver bullets in it.
哦，小心。里面有银子弹。
What's he thinking?
他在想什么？
He's got more paranoid
他变得更偏执了
since he saw the footage from the hospital.
自从他看了医院的录像。
What footage?
什么录像？
This guy just seemed to fly from a cab to the front door.
这家伙似乎直接从出租车飞到了前门。
I'm such an idiot.
我真是个白痴。
Why didn't I look for surveillance cameras?
我为什么没找监控摄像头？
Wait a minute, you-- No, no. We didn't do anything.
等等，你——不，不。我们没做什么。
It was-- it was our stem, Cisserus.
是——是我们的源头，西瑟勒斯。
She's a monster.
她是个怪物。
She's gonna louse it up for all of us.
她会把我们所有人都搞砸的。
Don't trip. We'll talk to Tepish.
别紧张。我们会和泰皮什谈谈。
Oh, I saw him after work
哦，我下班后见过他
and he said you'll be feeling better soon.
他说你很快就会感觉好些的。
You're just pregnant.
你只是怀孕了。
What?
什么？
I'm pregnant? We're gonna have a baby.
我怀孕了？我们要有孩子了。
I'm pregnant!
我怀孕了！
Oh, my God!
哦，我的天！
Oh, I can't believe this. I'm pregnant?
哦，我不敢相信。我怀孕了？
You want a baby?
你想要孩子吗？
Well...
嗯…
yeah.
是的。
I'm over 40. How many more chances am I gonna get?
我四十多岁了。我还能有多少机会？
And besides, I'll make a kick-ass father.
再说，我会是个超赞的爸爸。
All right.
好吧。
Forget cell phones, forget iPhones,
忘了手机，忘了iPhone，
forget PowerBooks, forget iPads.
忘了PowerBook，忘了iPad。
Yay.
耶。
Now I can do everything I want
现在我可以做任何我想做的事
with my iPad Mini.
用我的iPad Mini。
That looks just like your phone.
那看起来就像你的手机。
But it doesn't make calls.
但它不能打电话。
I got my tweets, I got my e-mails,
我有我的推特，我有我的邮件，
I got my friends, I got my alerts, I got--
我有我的朋友，我有我的提醒，我有——
So as the day progresses, you can read
所以随着一天过去，你可以阅读
thousands of unsolicited messages,
成千上万的不请自来的消息，
advertisements, and the mindless brain vomit of acquaintances?
广告，以及熟人们无意识的大脑呕吐物？
Someone sounds hormonal.
有人听起来荷尔蒙失调了。
Maybe you're pregnant, too!
也许你也怀孕了！
So annoying.
太烦人了。
You have to keep learning to use new crap
你必须不断学习使用新的垃圾
that doesn't actually do anything better
实际上并没有比旧的垃圾
than the old crap, which is incompatible with the new crap,
做得更好，而旧的垃圾与新的垃圾不兼容，
all so you can have blogs and watch fake teenagers
所有这些都是为了让你有博客和看假的青少年
and real housewives?
和真正的家庭主妇？
And it's all happening too fast
这一切发生得太快了
and I'm tired.
我累了。
I'm just sick and tired of it all.
我只是厌倦了这一切。
It's okay.
没关系。
We don't have to get the iPad Minis.
我们不必买iPad Mini。
No, I'm sorry...
不，我很抱歉…
Look. Only a couple stations, but they had Groucho Marx.
看。只有几个台，但他们有格劳乔·马克斯。
No, that's not Groucho.
不，那不是格劳乔。
Groucho was the mustache guy.
格劳乔是那个有胡子的人。
Yeah, he had glasses and a cigar.
是的，他戴眼镜抽雪茄。
Yeah, a cigar and glasses.
是的，雪茄和眼镜。
You'll split $25 between you. Are you ready?
你们将平分25美元。你们准备好了吗？
Yes. Who is buried in Grant's Tomb?
是的。谁埋在格兰特墓？
Were people really that stupid?
人们真的那么蠢吗？
No, that's what he'd ask when he felt bad
不，那是他感觉不好时会问的
and wanted to give 'em a few bucks.
想给他们几块钱。
Is Grant's Tomb in New York?
格兰特墓在纽约吗？
No. No. Yeah. Yeah.
不。不。是的。是的。
Have any of you ever been there?
你们有人去过那里吗？
No. No.
不。不。
- That's it.
- What?
- 就是它。
- 什么？
God, the place no New Yorker ever goes.
天哪，那个没有纽约人会去的地方。
Of course, Cisserus would want a monument.
当然，西瑟勒斯会想要一个纪念碑。
And it's got a tomb.
它还有个墓。
Oh, my God. You're probably right.
哦，我的天。你可能说对了。
Come on.
来吧。
Show me again. Yeah, here.
再给我看看。是的，这里。
I guess I totally can tell, but it's--
我想我完全能看出来，但是它——
it's like, I don't know. I always thought you'd be
它就像，我不知道。我一直以为你会是
the first one to have a baby. Is that weird?
第一个有孩子的。那很奇怪吗？
But now that it's happening-- Listen.
但现在它正在发生——听着。
You have to decide something independent of me or Joey.
你必须独立于我或乔伊做出决定。
This baby won't survive in your condition.
这个孩子在你的状态下无法存活。
If you want it, you have to turn back.
如果你想要它，你必须变回去。
How does that even--
那怎么——
Cisserus would have to be killed.
西瑟勒斯必须被杀死。
That's right.
没错。
I'd be in my '40s.
我会四十多岁。
But I'd be a mom.
但我会是个妈妈。
You'd be older, too. I know.
你也会变老。我知道。
I can't decide for the both of us.
我不能替我们俩做决定。
How do you feel about not being young anymore?
你对不再年轻有什么感觉？
Which part--
哪部分——
running around to clubs and dating idiots?
跑俱乐部和约会白痴？
Would be nice not to have to fake all the references.
不必伪造所有引用会很好。
Ugh. Like acting nostalgic over
呃。像是对
"Hey, Arnold" instead of "Happy Days."
《嘿，阿诺德》而不是《欢乐时光》表现怀旧。
Not to mention the slang, "BTW."
更不用说俚语，“BTW”。
And the clothes and the music.
还有衣服和音乐。
Staying young is getting old.
保持年轻正在变老。
Plus, we'll have a baby.
再说，我们会有一个孩子。
What are we even talking about? We can't kill Cisserus.
我们到底在说什么？我们杀不了西瑟勒斯。
She's lasted hundreds of years.
她活了几百年了。
But that's because nobody knew where she was.
但那是因为没人知道她在哪里。
But she's very sturdy.
但她很强壮。
And let's face it, we're wimps.
让我们面对现实吧，我们是懦夫。
Yeah, but she's sloppy. And conceited.
是的，但她很邋遢。而且自负。
And we'll call in the heavy-hitters.
我们会请来重量级人物。
Who?
谁？
Your future father-in-law.
你未来的岳父。
I just have to do one thing first.
我得先做一件事。
You said for a little more time, you'd do anything.
你说为了多一点时间，你什么都愿意做。
Did you mean it? Of course, but what can I do?
你是认真的吗？当然，但我能做什么？
Would you change your schedule and stay up later
你会改变你的日程安排，晚点起床
and promise to let her only have animals?
并保证让她只吃动物吗？
Now, wait a minute. Can you keep her alive?
现在，等等。你能让她活下去吗？
Not exactly alive. But not dead?
不完全是活着。但不是死了？
I can't but he can.
我不能，但他能。
It's up to you. Yeah.
这取决于你。是的。
Yeah, I can't lose her.
是的，我不能失去她。
I need privacy to do this.
我需要隐私来做这个。
Ah.
啊。
That's enough. It doesn't take that long.
够了。不需要那么长时间。
Your wife is very sweet.
你妻子很甜美。
Yeah. So, uh...
是的。所以，呃…
I am just wondering,
我只是想知道，
are you guys getting along, or, uh...
你们相处得好吗，或者，呃…
any chance of breaking up in the future?
未来有分手的可能吗？
Danny.
丹尼。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You're welcome.
不客气。
Come on, open up.
来吧，开门。
Who's there? I'm a friend of your son.
谁在那儿？我是你儿子的朋友。
I wanna help you. You want to help me?
我想帮你。你想帮我？
I've got some news for you, Grandpa.
我有些消息要告诉你，爷爷。
Did you say Grandpa?
你说了爷爷？
I thought all victims turned into vampires or died.
我以为所有受害者都会变成吸血鬼或者死亡。
I've never heard of anyone turning back.
我从未听说过有人变回来。
Well, I've never known anyone firsthand.
嗯，我从未亲身认识过任何人。
But apparently, if you're young enough--
但显然，如果你足够年轻——
those are useless on a stem.
那些对源头没用。
Are you really sure this isn't just Joey's rebelliousness?
你真的确定这不仅仅是乔伊的叛逆吗？
I mean, do they seem serious?
我的意思是，他们看起来是认真的吗？
Well, I've never seen Stacy like this before.
嗯，我从未见过斯泰茜这样。
And he's so excited to be a dad.
他当爸爸那么兴奋。
I believe they really are in love.
我相信他们是真的相爱。
When did you awaken?
你是什么时候被唤醒的？
1841.
1841年。
I survived a feeding and begged her to turn me.
我从一次吸食中幸存下来，求她转化我。
You wanted to become a vampire?
你想成为吸血鬼？
It was the lesser of two infections.
这是两种感染中较轻的一种。
In 1840, there was an epidemic of cholera
1840年，霍乱流行
in lower Manhattan.
在曼哈顿下城。
It was a painful and degrading death.
那是一种痛苦而有辱人格的死亡。
My husband and sisters had all passed.
我的丈夫和姐妹都去世了。
But, miraculously, my children were fine.
但是，奇迹般地，我的孩子们没事。
Not to be indelicate, but I had digestive rumblings
恕我冒昧，但我有消化不良的咕噜声
that I knew were the early symptoms,
我知道那是早期症状，
and orphans did not fare well in those days.
而孤儿在那些日子里过得不好。
So did your kids survive?
所以你的孩子们幸存了吗？
My son lived to the ripe old age of 63.
我儿子活到了63岁高龄。
And my daughter married Peter Meester,
我女儿嫁给了彼得·梅斯特，
and lived to be 99.
活到了99岁。
Unprecedented at the time.
当时是前所未有的。
Well, not many elderly people had strong young mothers
嗯，没有多少老年人有强壮年轻的母亲
to look out for them.
来照顾他们。
After the grandchildren, it would've been hard
有了孙辈之后，会很难
to stay in their lives and not scare them.
留在他们生活中而不吓到他们。
- Did you get that?
- Got it.
- 你拿到那个了吗？
- 拿到了。
You know, the only surefire way is to behead her.
你知道，唯一万无一失的方法是砍掉她的头。
Everything else might just piss her off.
其他一切可能只会惹恼她。
And when Cisserus is dead,
当西瑟勒斯死了，
Stacy will be a normal girl.
斯泰茜会是个正常的女孩。
Normal for Stacy.
对斯泰茜来说是正常的。
But, what happens to you, then?
但是，那你怎么办？
I saved my kids.
我救了我的孩子们。
Let's go save yours.
我们去救你的吧。
Here you go. Here's your family tree.
给你。这是你的家谱。
Your living descendants.
你活着的后代。
A great-great-great-great grandson.
一个曾曾曾曾孙子。
A drug addict. Incarcerated.
一个瘾君子。被监禁。
Four doctors. One in Doctors Without Borders.
四个医生。一个在无国界医生组织。
Two professors, four teachers,
两个教授，四个老师，
and in the House of Representatives,
在众议院，
Jane Rutherford, who chairs several committees.
简·卢瑟福，主持几个委员会。
She looks like you.
她长得像你。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
All right, leave the guns.
好了，放下枪。
Bring the axes, hatchets, blades.
带上斧头，手斧，刀刃。
All right, let's go get this dried up bitch.
好了，我们去抓住这个干瘪的婊子。
Well, I don't go to those places much, either.
嗯，我也不常去那些地方。
But it just shows you can meet someone really nice.
但这只是表明你可以遇到真正好的人。
Well, I never go to those places, so...
嗯，我从不去那些地方，所以…
I can't believe I met you, though.
我不敢相信我遇到了你。
You are beautiful. You're so sweet.
你很漂亮。你真甜。
Would you like to sit? Oh, would I?
你想坐吗？哦，我当然想。
Nice here. Isn't it?
这里很好。不是吗？
Oh.
哦。
Isn't your wife worried about
你妻子不担心
where you are so late?
你这么晚在哪儿吗？
She's on a trip and what she don't know won't hurt her.
她在旅行，她不知道的事不会伤害她。
Aren't you a bad boy?
你不是个坏小子吗？
I can be very bad.
我可能非常坏。
So what does a dirty boy like you do for a living?
那么像你这样的坏小子靠什么谋生？
I'm a dentist.
我是个牙医。
You're a dentist?
你是牙医？
What a lucky break.
真是好运。
Because I have something I'm really concerned about.
因为我有件事真的很担心。
Can I show you?
我能给你看看吗？
I've never seen anything like that in my--
我从未见过这样的东西在我——
Oh, no! No!
哦，不！不！
Run! Get out of here!
跑！离开这里！
You asshole.
你这个混蛋。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
You bad girls.
你们这些坏女孩。
I am very disappointed in you.
我对你们很失望。
After all I've done for you,
在我为你们做了这么多之后，
this is how you pay me back?
你们就是这样回报我的？
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
Who treats their stem like this?
谁这样对待他们的源头？
Those needed gunpowder!
那些需要火药！
Duck!
蹲下！
Oh, my God. We did it.
哦，我的天。我们做到了。
No. You guys, we have to get her into the tomb.
不。你们，我们必须把她弄进墓里。
Help me. Okay, okay.
帮我。好的，好的。
Argh.
啊。
When did my ass get so flat?
我的屁股什么时候变得这么平了？
Can I just say-- ow!
我能说一句吗——嗷！
Wait-- what are we gonna do about the body?
等等——我们怎么处理尸体？
Oh, it'll die in a minute.
哦，它一分钟内就会死掉。
Where were you?
你去哪儿了？
What? You asked me to get a chainsaw.
什么？你让我去拿电锯。
I get halfway here and realize it needs gasoline.
我走到一半才意识到它需要汽油。
Do you know where to get gasoline
你知道哪里能买到汽油吗
at 4:00 in the morning?
在凌晨4点？
Why didn't you get it where you got the saw?
你为什么不在你拿锯子的地方买？
Because I thought you plugged them in.
因为我以为你是插电的。
What am I, a lumberjack?
我是什么，伐木工人？
In the forest, you're plugging things in?
在森林里，你是插东西的？
- Yes, like a hairdryer or a--
- Joey!
- 是的，像是吹风机或者一个——
- 乔伊！
Come on! Come on! I don't believe this.
来吧！来吧！我不敢相信这个。
Hurry! Hurry.
快点！快点。
Okay, close it...
好的，关上它…
Whoa. Okay, let's go.
哇哦。好的，我们走吧。
You feel anything?
你感觉到什么了吗？
No.
不。
Wait.
等等。
That's it?
就这样？
You've aged 20 years?
你老了20岁？
Well, I didn't drink, smoke, do drugs, or sunbathe.
嗯，我不喝酒，不抽烟，不吸毒，也不晒日光浴。
Oh, well, maybe your genes just aren't as good.
哦，嗯，也许你的基因就是没那么好。
But with Botox and laser resurfacing...
但是用肉毒杆菌和激光换肤…
Don't tell me you lied about your age.
别告诉我你谎报了年龄。
Oh, come on.
哦，拜托。
Who the hell names their kid Goody anymore?
现在谁他妈的还给孩子起名叫古蒂？
You won't get any older, will you?
你不会再变老了，对吧？
It's okay.
没关系。
I've been around long enough.
我活得够久了。
I'm tired.
我累了。
I should've known.
我早该知道的。
Every time I turned on the History Channel,
每次我打开历史频道，
all I saw was stuff about Hitler.
我看到的都是关于希特勒的东西。
Don't be sad. I was gonna go into the sun before I met you.
别难过。在我遇见你之前我就打算走进阳光里了。
You showed me how to have fun.
你教会了我如何找乐子。
Is there anything you want?
你想要什么吗？
Yes.
是的。
I don't wanna be here.
我不想在这里。
I want to be in the center of things.
我想在事物的中心。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
You all right?
你还好吗？
You all right? How do you feel?
你还好吗？你感觉怎么样？
Hungry.
饿了。
How about one of those pretzel things?
那种椒盐脆饼怎么样？
Joey, can you go get one of those pretzel things?
乔伊，你能去买一个那种椒盐脆饼吗？
Of course. Thanks.
当然。谢谢。
Goody. Goody.
古蒂。古蒂。
Oh, my God.
哦，我的天。
Oh!
哦！
Hey, I saw that.
嘿，我看到了。
What? She looked at me. I wasn't doing anything.
什么？她看着我。我没做什么。
Need I remind you that I gave you
需要我提醒你我给了你
the best years of my life? Best years of my life.
我生命中最好的年华吗？我生命中最好的年华。
Yeah, and I'm not talking five, 10 years here.
是的，我不是在说五年，十年这里。
We're talking infinity.
我们在说无限。
Do you have any idea what that's like?
你知道那是什么感觉吗？
I'm starting to get an idea.
我开始有点明白了。
All right, Goody. Watch this.
好吧，古蒂。看这个。
Too frightening.
太吓人了。
Is it too frightening?
是不是太吓人了？
Bleh!
哇！
Well, you got Grandpa that time.
嗯，你这次吓到爷爷了。